https://www.capescottwatertaxi.ca/privacy-policy/

Online Privacy Statement
We collect personal information from our customers in the regular course of doing business. This statement answers some of your most frequently asked questions, and lets you know exactly how we’re protecting the information you entrust to us.
What personal information do you collect about me?
If you fill out the “Make a Booking” form we collect the following information about you:
Name
Phone Number
Email Address
If you choose to fill the other optional fields we ask for;
Address
City
State/Province
ZIP/Postal Code
Country
Fax
Organization
When you visit our web site, we also collect:
Information about your computer, including the type of operating system and browser you use, and your computer’s location.
What pages you visit on our site and what links you click on.
How do you use this information?
The main reasons we collect personal information from you are:
Customer service.
To complete a sale/transaction.
Marketing Analysis.
Periodically send emails to customers relevant to orders or quotes.
Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties
We do not share your personal information with any third parties.
Get in touch
We service: The North Coast Trail, Port Hardy, Port McNeill, Rivers Inlet, Shushartie Bay, Bella Bella, Drury Inlet, Sayward, Klemtu, Calvert Island, Burnette Bay, Smiths Inlet, Seymour Inlet, Kingcome Inlet, Knights Inlet and more.
CONTACT US FOR RATES & RESERVATIONS
Office Location 6555 Hardy Bay Road,
Box 580 Port Hardy,
© Copyright - Cape Scott Water Taxi Ltd. - All rights reserved | Website by Webacom
FacebookInstagramTwitterSitemap
Privacy Policy
Scroll to top
